<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Your Favorite Thing Sucks]]></title><description><![CDATA[A hate blog for just about everything]]></description><link>http://www.epicaricacy.com</link><generator>metalsmith-feed</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 21:49:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><copyright><![CDATA[2016 Andy Steinberg]]></copyright><item><title><![CDATA[The Metric System]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the idiocy of many humans, humanity itself continues to improve at most things. Technology, medicine, quality of life, access to information, productivity, and almost everything else we accomplish as a species is better now than it was before, and will be better in the future than it is now. However, sometimes we make mistakes and actually go backwards. Here I will cover a giant leap in the wrong direction made by nearly the entire world -- the metric system.</p>
<a name="post-excerpt"></a><p>To give you an indication of just how widespread this mistake was, according to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metric_system">Wikipedia</a>, the only countries that do not use the metric system as their primary system of measurement are the United States, Liberia, and Myanmar. That makes those three countries the three smartest in the world. There are many advocates in the United States for migrating to the metric system. Fortunately, common sense has thus far prevailed, and it remains a beacon of sanity in an insane world.</p>
<p>So what's wrong with the Metric system? It's simple. It was designed for scientific use in laboratories, equations, etc. It was <em>not</em> designed for every day use by the majority of the population. This is made obvious for a number of reasons across many of the different units of measure.</p>
<h2>Metric units are not magic</h2>
<p>First, let's agree that all base units are arbitrary. Here's how the metric units are defined:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metre">Meter</a> - the distance travelled by an object moving at the speed of light for 1/299,792,458 of a second. And how was that number decided upon? It was an approximation of 1,650,763.73 wavelengths in a vacuum of the radiation corresponding to the transition between the levels 2p10 and 5d5 of the krypton-86 atom. So what about that number? Well, it was just about equal to a platinum bar in France, when that bar is at a specified temperature and pressure, and is supported by two rollers. How did they figure out how long of a bar to make? It was just about 1/10,000,000 the distance between the North Pole and the Equator. That number was arbitrary.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kilogram">Kilogram</a> - the weight of a piece of metal in Paris. How was this weight decided? Well, it went through several revisions, but was essentially based on the weight of a cubic decimeter of water at 0 degrees Celsius in a vaccuum. That number was arbitrary.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ampere">Ampere</a> - 6.241 * 10 to the 18th power of the electric charge of a proton. This number was derived from the current that would deposit 0.001118000 grams of silver per second from a silver nitrate solution. That number was arbitrary.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Celsius">Celsius</a> - -273.15 degrees Celsius is defined as absolute zero and .01 degrees Celsius is defined as the triple point of water. That number was based on the freezing and boiling points of water at a pressure of one atmosphere being valued at zero and one-hundred, respectively. These numbers were not so arbitrary as those previous, but, as I will demonstrate, even they are not good numbers for common use.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Most other units are based on relating the above units to each other.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>For the remainder of this argument, I am going to be comparing the metric system to the imperial system used by the United States. I am not going to list the origins of imperial units because their history is not important. What is important is to demonstrate how the imperial units are at least based on useful approximations. I will tackle the different units in the same order as listed above.</p>
<h2>Length</h2>
<p>In regards to the meter, how often does your average person need to know how far light travels in an infintesimally small amount of time? Or when are they measuring the wavelengths of atomic radiation? More practically, when are they calculating the some fraction of the distance between Earth's North Pole and its equator? I'm going to go with never, never, and never on those.</p>
<p>The imperial system has units such as a foot, which is about the length of a human foot. Three of those are defined as a yard, which works out to a distance very close to a human stride. If you need more precision, you have inches, which are large enough that they're easy to eyeball and small enough that they're plenty precise enough for most tasks. Additionally, they're easy to map to fractions of a foot, which is something I'll get into later.</p>
<p>For longer distances, you have miles, which were originally defined as 1000 paces. An arbitrary number? Sure. But a useful arbirtary number. It was used heavily by travelers and militaries on the march. That's the key difference between metric and imperial. The former is meant for science, the latter is meant for practical use.</p>
<p>Do me a favor. The next time you're drawing out a makeshift baseball diamond, see what's faster: locating a meter stick or tape measure (or running out to procure one if you don't have one handy), or counting your strides. Which was faster? Easier? Cheaper?</p>
<h2>Mass / Weight</h2>
<p>The pound was defined in terms the weight of 7,000 grains of wheat, which was used heavily in trading. Now, it's defined in relation to a kilogram, making it equally as arbitrary as a kilogram. The big difference is that a pound is made up of 16 ounces, and a kilogram is made up of 1000 grams, and the 16 is more useful than the 1,000, which I will explain later on.</p>
<h2>Electric current</h2>
<p>Not applicable. There is no imperial unit.</p>
<h2>Temperature</h2>
<p>Let me ask you this, outside of science class or, if you are a professional scientist, your job, in what context are you referring to temperature the majority of the time? I'm going to guess that the answer, overwhelmingly, is the weather. But Celsius is not defined in terms of the weather, it's defined in terms of the physical states of water. You know what is defined in terms of weather? Fahrenheit. The scale of zero degrees to one-hundred degrees maps very closely to the liveable temperatures of the human being. When you go above or below that range, human life starts to become dangerous without accounting for those extremes.</p>
<p>When given a temperature in Fahrenheit, you can very quickly map that to a general weather forecast. You have a one-hundred point scale where numbers in the middle imply mildness and numbers closer to either end are your measures of hot and cold. Tell me how often one-hundred degrees Celsius comes up in your life.</p>
<h2>Conversions</h2>
<p>The most commonly made argument for the metric system is how easy it is to convert from one unit to another. A meter is 100 centimeters. A liter is 1000 milliliters (never mind how unuseful a single milliliter is to anything practical). So all you have to do to convert is move the decimal. This works well if you're writing numbers on paper, but let's say you're doing some woodwork, and someone says, &quot;Cut me a third of a meter.&quot; 0.33333 repeating meters is not intuitive, so let's convert that to centimeters. Now you need to cut 33.33333 repeating. That's not any better. If someone says, &quot;Cut me a third of a yard,&quot; your response would probably be, &quot;So, a foot?&quot; A third of a foot? Four inches. How is that not an easier conversion?</p>
<p>The metric system's conversions have nothing to do with practicality, and everything to do with how many fingers are on the hands of the average human being. But if you're doing math in your head, 12 is a lot more useful than 10. It's divisible by 2, 3, 4, and 6. Ten, on the other hand, is divisible by 2 and 5. So even the most prominent argument for the metric system breaks down once you take it outside the laboratory. There's a reason steaks come in 6oz, 8oz, 10oz, 12oz, or 16oz increments and not whatever those work out to in grams. Because they're useful values that convert to easy fractions of a pound.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>That the metric system is better than the US Imperial system is a commonly accepted argument that very few people apply any real analysis too. This is problematic because that argument, in nearly every context in which it is made, is wrong. Metric works well in a scientific setting, but in real life application it falls short. Its measurement values just aren't based on common use cases. The United States is correct in continuing to use the Imperial system, even before you factor in the cost inherent in making the switch.</p>
<p>The metric system, as an every day system of measurement, sucks.</p>
]]></description><link>http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2016/07/10/the-metric-system</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2016/07/10/the-metric-system</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Steinberg]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Star Wars Episode VII: The Force Awakens]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>After viewing Episode II upon its release, my viewing group and I emerged from the theater, stood beneath the box office signs at the front of the theater, and performed a ritual that I'm sure many of you share, whereupon we clear up confusions, share opinions, and attempt to classify what we had just seen. To this day, I clearly remember a good friend of mine saying, “People will argue because of nostalgia, but that was the best Star Wars yet.” The rest of us stood there flabbergasted because Episode II was quite obviously not the best Star Wars yet, nor even very good to begin with.</p>
<p>Thirteen years later, I feel like I am reliving that moment. Only instead we are talking about Episode VII, and rather than it being my one friend, it is nearly everyone who has expressed an opinion to me or written a review that I've read on the internet. Perhaps people aren't saying that it was the best Star Wars, but they're positively comparing it to the original trilogy. And once again I am flabbergasted, because Episode VII was terrible.</p>
<!-- more --><a name="post-excerpt"></a>
<p>In this review, I will attempt to demonstrate that not only is Star Wars Episode VII: The Force Awakens a bad movie, it is in fact the worst movie in the series. I know this statement sets off a few alarms in many reader's heads. First, it looks like hyperbole. Second, it seems reactionary given the recency of its release. Third, considering the general praise that it has thus far received, it sounds contradictory for the sake of attention. I affirm that, despite appearances, it is none of those things, and that I firmly believe in my thesis.</p>
<p>Before continuing, understand that the review necessarily contains massive spoilers.</p>
<p><strong>DO NOT CONTINUE READING IF YOU HAVE NOT SEEN THE FILM AND DO NOT WANT TO BE SPOILED.</strong></p>
<h2>Plot</h2>
<p>To start with, I want to review the plot from a high level before getting into some of the details. The plot of this movie seems to be pretty simple, as things generally are in the Star Wars universe. Here was have a smaller subplot specific to Episode VII within a larger plot of what I assume will be this trilogy.</p>
<p>The former of those, the plot specific to this movie, is Star Wars: The Search For Skywalker. Everyone wants to find Luke. Which is understandable. Luke Skywalker is a Jedi. The last in existence (again, since he went from being the last in existence to having students to all of his students being…dead?).</p>
<p>The Resistance wants to find him so that they can…well they don't explain it, exactly. In fact, they don't explain anything about what the Resistance is trying to do. We don't see any glimpses into the ongoing war, we just know that there's a war over something. At no point is there any Resistance strategy to the war until like eleven planets get blown up, and the Resistance decides that they probably shouldn't let that happen again. So Luke fits into their lack of plans somehow. Maybe they need him to come up with a plan? Who knows?</p>
<p>The First Order wants to find Luke so that they can…what? Turn him to the dark side in order to win the war? No, that doesn't seem to be the plan. And what good would that do when they can blow up like eleven planets at a time? So that Kylo Ren can complete his transition to the Dark Side? Because that would be worse than, I don't know, murdering his father somehow? No, that can't be it. Also, Snoke says he can complete his training without Luke. So they can kill him so they don't have to fight him? No, he's a hermit and he's not fighting, so that can't be it. So the Resistance doesn't get him on their side and turn the tide of battle like he did in the war against the Empire? This seems to be the only reasonable explanation, though when they have a weapon that can blow up eleven planets at once, that doesn't seem like it should be a priority.</p>
<p>So everyone wants to find Luke, but the only real reason he's so important seems to be because Mark Hamill wants to get paid and his name will help sell movie tickets, I guess.</p>
<p>This brings up a couple things that don't make much sense. First is the Resistance. We know that a Republic exists, and we know that the Resistance and the Republic share a common enemy. If the Resistance is not the Republic's military, then why don't we see them? Why aren't the Resistance and the Republic teaming up? Who does the Resistance represent, what are its goals, and why is it not affiliated with the Republic? Seemingly, the Resistance is the Republic's military, and so why aren't they called the Republic or the Republic Army instead of the Resistance? Who are they resisting? The First Order? They're using the original trilogy Rebellion's ships and symbol, so why aren't they called the Rebellion? Presumably it's because the Empire seems to no longer exist, so they're not rebelling against anything. Does the Resistance only exist to resist the First Order? What military existed between the Empire and the First Order?</p>
<p>The second thing that doesn't make sense is The First Order. It appears that the Empire no longer exists, and the First Order represents what's left of its military. Does the First Order represent any actually population? Is it a group of planets? It appears to be nothing but a military force. A mercenary force without a master. Their only goal appears to be to destroy the Republic. But why? To rule? Revenge? These questions aren't answered. But it does lead to other questions. If they don't have a population, where are they getting their troops? They're landing on Republic or other planets and stealing children, and then brainwashing them into fighting? What reason are those troops given to fight? It's easier to brainwash someone to an actual cause than to convince them to fight just to fight. Where does the First Order get its resources? It built a weapon the size of a planet that eats suns. Where did they get the funds to build that? Who built it? The empire had a huge collection of planets, an enormous number of taxpayers, and rule over engineers, construction workers, and everyone else with the skills necessary for a project such as this. The First Order appears to have none of this. Everything was just magicked up for the sake of a movie.</p>
<p>Then you have the plot of the trilogy, which I guess is that the First Order wants to destroy the Republic, which is back somehow. So they start by blowing up the Republic's planets. They don't say which ones, but it's like eleven of them. And from the looks of it, heavily populated ones. And immediately before that, Hux gives a Hitler speech where he tells us that when they fire the gun, the Republic will be gone. So uhh, I guess that plot is over.</p>
<p>Except the Resistance still exists. So now you have an army but no government that it's fighting for and, what I assume is a heavily depleted population. At this point, you could call them a resistance force, as they are resisting The First Order. At least now the name “The Resistance” makes more sense.</p>
<p>But here's the thing. The First Order knows where The Resistance Army is. Their second target group are its military sites. But The First Order's plan is foiled because the Resistance, the only military force in the galaxy that is capable of stopping them, is still around to stop them. Why the hell wouldn't The First Order have destroyed the military first and then the government? There was a 100% chance of success if they did it that way.</p>
<p>And again, we still don't know The First Order's goal. In Episode IV, the Death Star is meant to intimidate the rebels. They're not trying to kill everyone. They make a strategic decision to sacrifice one planet (that they know to be home to rebels) in order to bring peace through the threat of force. The First Order seems to just want to blow shit up because it's cool. It's like the writers thought, “How do we one-up the Death Star? Let's make it even bigger and let it blow up lots of planets all at once! That's really evil!” Even terrorists have ultimate goals. Terror isn't the goal, it exists to serve some ultimate purpose. The First Order hasn't demonstrated any ultimate purpose outside of terror itself. It's not an interesting entity.</p>
<p>I want to contrast that with the Empire destroying Alderaan. In Episode IV, when that happens, there is a lot of emotional buildup. Leia's pleas to save the lives of billions of people serve to make the audience understand the level of catastrophe that they're about to witness. Obi-Wan's reaction reinforces this. And if you still don't get it, when the Milennium Falcon arrives to find Alderaan turned into nothing but chunks of rock, you can fully comprehend what has transpired. A lot of time is spent on screen to ensure that. In Episode VII, the level of destruction and death is multiples of that, and nobody seems to care at all. The only reaction we get is when people see the death lasers shooting across the sky and scream. I don't understand how they even know it's a bad thing, except maybe that it's red, and red lasers always mean something nefarious in the Star Wars universe. We don't even know the names of the planets that were destroyed. Thus, this event lacks all of the emotional impact that Alderaan had. JJ Abrams was simply trying to do something that looked cool and create something more evil than the Empire without having to do the legwork to earn it.</p>
<p>Let's specifically focus on the climactic scene where the Rebellion Resistance takes out the Death Star Starkiller using a fleet of fighters. First of all, the plan was far too complex to be successful. Especially since Stormtrooper Jar Jar said he had a plan that he couldn't reveal on how to take down their shields, which was step one out of like five that all had to go right and in order. And everyone just trusted him. And trusted that every other thing would go exactly right.</p>
<p>So Stormtrooper Jar Jar gets there and reveals, lo and behold, he doesn't know what to do. They decide to capture his former commanding officer and make her tell them what to do. What we know about her in particular and these troopers in general is that they are brainwashed, have no regard for human life, and live to serve Empire, not themselves. So how does it make sense that she'd agree to whatever they ask because they have a gun pointed at her? But she does, and falls back on simply making empty threats while acquiescing to their plans.</p>
<p>At some point Chewie set off some explosives, which did something, I'm not sure what, and then X-Wings started doing “bombing runs” on a thing despite the fact that they are air-to-air dogfighting ships and they should be using actual bombers like B-Wings to blow it up. But no, they use fighters that have to do repeated runs because they lack firepower.</p>
<p>Then Hux orders that all ships be deployed in defense of the Starkiller, a thing that is the size of like ten Death Stars. This turns out to be about a dozen TIE Fighters. How is that reasonable at all?</p>
<p>The Resistance needs to blow up the Starkiller before 100% of the nearby star has been absorbed, because for some unknown reason, the weapon cannot fire until 100% of the star has been absorbed. And also that the weapon will fire at the exact moment that the star is 100% absorbed. That means that the star that is being absorbed is the absolute minimum sized star that can power the weapon, or that every star has the exact same amount of stored energy, or that the writing was shoddy. I'm going to go with the last option.</p>
<p>Finally, I want to talk about the lightsaber duel between Kylo, Stormtrooper Jar Jar, and Rey, and how it reveals one of the most severe problems in Episode VII, which is the inconsistency of the power of the force. Kylo begins by fighting Stormtrooper Jar Jar, who is wielding a lightsaber that he has used once before, in a fight against a random Stormtrooper, in which he lost badly. Kylo has force powers and training in using the force and lightsaber combat.</p>
<p>Briefly, let's go back to the Episode V fight between Luke and Vader. At this point, Luke has had some training and is at least somewhat able to channel the force. And Vader wrecks him. Hard. Eventually Vader puts his lightsaber away and just throws shit at him because that's all he needs to do against a lesser foe.</p>
<p>I'm not saying Kylo Ren is Vader, but Stormtrooper Jar Jar sure as shit isn't Luke. And Ren struggles to beat him. Like, takes a few licks first. And can't even finish him off before Rey gets up. What happens when Rey gets up? She beats the everloving shit out of Kylo. At this point, Rey has never wielded a lightsaber in her life, and only realizes she has force powers during the fight itself! Granted, Kylo was injured. He had just taken a direct hit from a bowcaster that, previously, was shown to take out multiple stormtroopers in a single shot. But Kylo just has a flesh wound for some reason that's probably thoughtless writing like so many other things.</p>
<p>When Episode I introduced Darth Maul, they had a fun, well-choreographed lightsaber fight with him vs. two Jedi. It was the best lightsaber fight in the entire series. At the conclusion of it, they killed Darth Maul, because he had served his purpose. He didn't have a personality, he was there to look cool and have a fantastic duel. Mission: accomplished.</p>
<p>Kylo Ren was a less good at fighting, less cool looking Darth Maul, but they decided he needed to be kept alive for some reason, so a rift showed up out of nowhere before Rey could finish him off. And even though she's instantly good at everything she tries, I guess she doesn't know about force jump yet. It was a completely contrived scenario that could have been handled immensely better, and instead left me throwing my hands up in the air towards the screen in disbelief at how badly done it was.</p>
<p>Contrast this with Kylo Ren at the beginning of the movie who is holding blaster fire in the air while doing other things and in general running around being Vader-like. The discrepancy of his power level at the tail ends of the movie does a huge disservice to him as a character and the concept of the force as a whole.</p>
<h2>Sentimentality and Nostalgia</h2>
<p>I don't have a lot to say about nostalgia except that every time they try it, it feels heavy-handed or even, at times, dishonest. Indeed, a lot of the plot points and characters tie directly back into the original trilogy. You have a new Jedi / aspiring pilot just discovering their powers (Luke / Rey). You have a charismatic pilot (Han, Poe). You have a masked, auto-tuned villain in black who likes to use the force to hurt people (Vader / Ren). You have a cute boopity-bop Droid (R2-D2 / BB-8). You have a planet shattering weapon (Death Star, Starkiller) that needs to be destroyed using X-Wings. You have a search for an old Jedi Master (Kenobi / Luke). You have your origins on a desert planet (Tatooine / Jakuu). You have a place to get information and travel full of all kinds of aliens (Cantina / Maz's Place). You have an evil military leader (Tarkin / Hux). You have the enigmatic, sinister overlord (Emperor, Snoke). You have Han Solo being hunted down for money that he owes. You have the tragic death of one of our heroes (Kenobi, Han). And there's tons more.</p>
<p>It's pretty obvious that the movie was meant to mirror Episode IV. People are forgiving it because it was trying to introduce Star Wars while still being Star Wars. But the plot of Episode IV is not what made it Star Wars. And let's not forget that Episode I had to accomplish the same thing. And while maybe that wasn't a good movie, at least it tried to do something different. Episode VII vas lazy, and tried to leverage the goodness of its predecessors as a way of being warmly received. It's a cheap tactic that seems to have worked on most people, but I think it's heinous.</p>
<p>Additionally, you get this weird sentimental shit like when Han and Leia reunite. There's a romance movie moment where she puts her head in his chest and closes her eyes and smiles or something dumb, and the camera holds it for like five seconds. This is the woman we are supposed to believe is the commanding general of the entire Resistance military. The same Leia that was fierce and independent in the original movies and her relationship with Han wasn't lovey dovey at all like we're seeing. It feels fake and inconsistent with what we know about those characters, and their relationship is less likeable or interesting this way.</p>
<h2>Characters</h2>
<h3>Leia</h3>
<p>Speaking of Leia, what the hell happened to her? She's the general of the army (outranking Ackbar somehow) and yet she doesn't seem to know what she's doing or even care that much. Maybe that's why the Resistance is fiddling its thumbs. She needs to ask people like Stormtrooper Jar Jar for ideas. She's also too weak to be mad at Han for bailing on her, and she's too weak to go after her estranged serial killer son herself, so she asks Han to do it. Leia went from strong female heroine to feckless waste of screen space. It reminds me of what Indiana Jones IV did to Marion's character, only this time you can't blame George Lucas.</p>
<h3>Han</h3>
<p>Han mostly gets out of this movie unscathed, probably thanks to Harrison Ford's talent and charisma. His death scene, which I'll get to, was awfully done, and the aforementioned scene with Leia was bad. The only other part that I thought sucked was when the two different criminal organizations worked together (which doesn't entirely make sense to me) to approach him at the same time demanding money, so we could have a forced “Same ol' Han!” moment. In that scene, Han Solo seemed more like a caricature of himself than anything else.</p>
<h3>Luke</h3>
<p>Here's what we know about Luke. He tried to train a bunch of Jedi, including Kylo Ren. Kylo Ren did something (killed? recruited?) all of them and then escaped. Luke, having let this happen somehow, got super depressed and became a hermit. This is the same Luke who abandoned all reason multiple times in order to help his friends and the Rebellion in the original trilogy. Now he runs away and stares at oceans off of cliff sides all day long. Unless someone shows up and then he stares at their hands forever. And we're supposed to feel relieved when they find him.</p>
<h3>R2-D2</h3>
<p>He's in standby mode because he's depressed because one friend of his (of many) is in hiding. Does that seem at all like R2 to anyone? And then he comes out of it because they have the star map and he can go find his friend, except that even when they get the star map he still stays depressed for a while. Even though he has the star map that can lead everyone to his friend. He doesn't go off standby mode until later for absolutely no reason that can be explained. Why does he need to come out of standby? Because he has a star map that no other computer in the entire Resistance, or any ally of the Resistance, has. There's no explanation for how or why that happened.</p>
<h3>BB-8</h3>
<p>Let's call him what he is. Star Wars Wall-E, a character made to sell merchandise to people who already have R2-D2 shit, and move on.</p>
<h3>Maz</h3>
<p>Before entering Maz's place, Han tells his traveling party not to stare at anything. Because why? Because that makes the next scene more ominous. Except that Maz's place has no danger about it, Maz is a completely nice person. We go in expecting some kind of crafty character with questionable alliances, but instead we get someone who is wholeheartedly good and helpful. The denizens don't seem dangerous either. They even seem happy to take Stormtrooper Jar Jar wherever he wants to go with no questions asked. Maz also has Luke's lightsaber but they can't explain why that makes sense because &quot;it's a long story.&quot; The one time the writers indicate that they aren't actually explaining something that doesn't make sense, and they excuse it away. Is their laziness and ineptitude not transparent to everyone? And oh yeah the lightsaber has magic memory powers now.</p>
<h3>Poe</h3>
<p>When writing the movie, someone probably said, “Hey let's combine Han Solo's 'tude with Wedge's piloting” and then JJ Abrams, if it wasn't his idea originally, thought that was just wonderful. They gloss over how he survived the crash, didn't run into Stormtrooper Jar Jar, didn't seem to try to look for the droid that was the entire reason he was on the planet in the first place, and escaped without The First Order finding him. They also decided to make him the best fighter pilot in the history of the galaxy. Well, at least until Rey gets two minutes of flying time under her belt. There's a scene where he gets like six confirmed kills in three seconds. Why does The Resistance even have other pilots? Just send him in to take out the entire First Order. You can give him any gunner, because he apparently can train them to fire the guns on a ship he has never flown or gunned from before, while flying the ship he has never flown before better than anyone has ever flown it. At least if that gunner has the Luck of Jar Jar trait, anyway. Because in this movie, if you have a name, and you're not Stormtrooper Jar Jar, then you're the best person in the galaxy at whatever you specialize in. Or you're Rey and you're the best person in the galaxy at absolutely everything, but more on that in a bit. Also, one thing Poe and Stormtrooper Jar Jar have in common is they like to say things like, “Wow that person is a great ______” whenever someone with a name does something ridiculously well, just so that the audience can keep up and understand that the character with a name is really good at the thing that they do!</p>
<h3>Rey</h3>
<p>One of the stupid things Episode VII does is dumb down the force. Previously, you couldn't just be strong in the force to be able to wield it purposefully. The ways in which Episode IV Luke or Episode I Anakin were able to use the force was passively. It helped them with things like intuition or reaction. Actual mastery over techniques took a willing teacher and extensive training. But this movie couldn't wait for any of that, so it created Rey -- the force user who is good at everything she attempts, but who also learns specific force powers in a matter of minutes. Force powers that, historically, only a Jedi Master could summon (such as Force Persuade), and she can learn them before she even fully recognizes that she has the ability to wield the force at all (as seen when the realization comes to her during a lightsaber fight, during which, once she realizes it, is able to go into a meditative state whilst pushing against Kylo Ren's lightsaber, and then come out of the state more powerful than before, which is not something that any other Jedi has done ever). Here is a list of all the things that Rey is immediately a galaxy-class expert at the first time she attempts them: piloting the Millennium Falcon, repairing or altering complex electrical systems, being a deadeye with a blaster mid-combat, lightsaber dueling, force persuasion, force mind reading, force mind reading resistance. She's so good, that when the gun on the Falcon breaks such that it's stuck in one firing position that she can't see, in a direction she can't see, she's able to evade enemy fire, drastically change speeds, flip the Falcon around aim the cannon exactly at a moving, oncoming enemy TIE Fighter such that all Stormtrooper Jar Jar has to do is pull the trigger. This is the most over-the-top maneuver in the entire series by a substantial margin and it's performed by someone with no experience doing it. It makes Han successfully navigating an asteroid field look simple. If C-3PO were there, calculating the odds would have caused an overflow error.</p>
<h3>Kylo Ren</h3>
<p>I could probably write an entire review about how horrible Kylo Ren is, but here is the thing that I think sums it up the best. What made Darth Vader awesome was two things. One is that he starts off as the most menacing villain of all time. Anyone who challenges this fact learns quickly and severely how bad an idea that is. And yet the original trilogy is about Vader's redemption. It is his inner and outer struggle to overcome his previous mistakes, to get out of the hole he has dug himself, and to do what's right and good in the end. You would never guess that by the end of Episode VI, you'd be rooting for the fellow.</p>
<p>Here's why that's not going to happen with Kylo Ren. Because his struggle is that he has good parents and a supportive family and he has to fight everything they taught him and raised him to be so that he can willingly be evil. Vader wasn't willingly evil. He was manipulated into it. He's been convinced that what he's doing is the right thing. Not Ren. He's conscious of the choices he's making. He's completely and utterly unsympathetic, and the only reason we're given is so that he can be like Grandpa Annie.</p>
<p>History is written by the victors. You know who won in Episode VI? Luke. Luke won. Luke gets to tell everyone the truth behind Vader and the Emperor. He can emphasize Anakin Skywalker's redemption. You think Kylo Ren only hears the Episode IV stories of Vader? Hell no. He knows the whole thing. He knows Vader wasn't the purely evil man in black that he's trying to emulate. He just ignores it.</p>
<p>What makes an interesting villain is when they believe they are doing good. Maybe it's that the ends justify the means, or maybe they truly believe that the means themselves are good. For one reason or another, they are not doing good, or are at least doing enough harm that the good isn't justified. That's a villain. Kylo Ren doesn't seem to believe that he's doing anything good. He wants to be bad for badness sake. How can a character like this be at all compelling?</p>
<p>He's just a rebellious kid. But what is he rebelling against? His parents weren't strict. There's no mention of regret between Han and Leia for anything wrong they did in bringing him up. They let him train with his savior of the galaxy, all-around good guy who saved Vader's soul Uncle Luke. His father is literally the coolest dude in the entire galaxy. And he's emo about all of that?</p>
<p>And let's talk about Han's death, which is easily the worst part of the movie. Han shows up, is willing to ignore / forgive all the evil things that his son has done. Han says he can still come home, that he's still loved, that his parents accept him for who he is. It's absolutely everything you'd want in a parent. And then Kylo, in a scene that's as telegraphed as they come, says he needs Han's help to do what he needs to do, which we all know is kill Han. And Han says that he'll do anything to help his son. Which apparently meant, “Put your hand on my lightsaber so that I can kill you.” What? How does that help Kylo overcome his conscience at all? Han didn't egg him on. He didn't offer him anything but support. If anything, that action would have the exact opposite effect of what Kylo wanted. But the lazy writers thought that would give Kylo Ren depth somehow. See, look? He's complex because he just said he was. No, sorry writers. It doesn't work that way. He's completely empty. He's a shell of a character. Kylo Ren is the worst character in the history of Star Wars, and that's including Jar Jar and also…</p>
<h3>Stormtrooper Jar Jar</h3>
<p>Let's compare Jar Jar and Stormtrooper Jar Jar. Both of them are alienated from their home. Both of them are clumsy and constantly falling over or getting captured. Both of them are bad at pretty much everything they attempt, but then stumble/luck into succeeding. Both of them lie about who they are because they are nobodies but want to be taken seriously. Both of them feel a half step out of sync with everyone else, like they are in a movie and say things that make no sense within their own world, but only make sense to us, the viewers who inhabit a totally different world. Thing that seem to only be there to appeal to children. Both of them are essentially tagalongs to the people who actually matter. Both of them exist to offer commentary on what's happening in the world. How many times does Stormtrooper Jar Jar point out a character who just did something really well? Who else but Jar Jar would utter a line like, “Droid, please?” Who else but Jar Jar would get captured by a monster that, up until the point where he was captured, mutilated everyone they came upon immediately, but in this case, for some unknown reason, the monster decided to instead drag him off to somewhere giving the heroes a chance to save him? Who else would make humorous remarks while getting dragged away to presumably their grotesque death at the hands of said monster? Who else would luck into getting saved from the monster? Who else would go into the enemy base without a plan and then somehow succeed despite that? Face it, Stormtrooper Jar Jar is Jar Jar. The only difference is that he doesn't talk in a ridiculous voice or make cartoonish facial expressions. If you think Episode I is bad because it has Jar Jar as a major character, well Episode VII has Stormtrooper Jar Jar.</p>
<h2>The Good Stuff</h2>
<p>Not everything was bad. The dogfighting was some of the best in the series. Chewie is cool as always, and so is his bowcaster, which got way more use than it ever has previously and I was happy to see that. Han Solo was good in most of his scenes. And the effects were cool and didn't get in the way, which can't be said about the prequels. That's about it.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>I think at this point I've given enough evidence to show that Episode VII is not a good movie. Yet I go beyond that and consider it to be the worst Star Wars film, and here's why. It doesn't offer anything new and it doesn't do anything important well. The characters are flatter than in any other movie. They are archetypes of archetypes, with no flaws whatsoever. The prequels tried new things. They had new stories and new characters. Some of those characters were really good, such as Qui-Gon.</p>
<p>Another difference is that a lot of the things that people hate about Episode I or the other prequels, you could remove and not lose much, if anything. You can take out Jar Jar and not miss much. You can delete Anakin's escapades on the Naboo Fighter or any mention of midichlorians and have the same movie. But in Episode VII, every major character is bad. The plot is bad. The fight scenes that aren't dogfights are bad. You can't take this stuff out and still have a movie. You have nothing. If you erase Kylo Ren then you have lost your villain. If you get rid of Rey then you've lost pretty much everything else.</p>
<p>George Lucas made Episode I for children. JJ Abrams made Episode VII for….children too slow to understand Episode I?</p>
]]></description><link>http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2015/12/19/star-wars-episode-vii-the-force-awakens</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2015/12/19/star-wars-episode-vii-the-force-awakens</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Steinberg]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Soccer]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>The 2014 World Cup recently began in Brazil, a nation lacking in the sanitation, infrastructure, public safety, and financial resources that are usually required to host an international spectacle of this level. Yet, one other thing acts as a larger blight over the event than any of these others. That is the sport of soccer itself. I believe that soccer is an objectively bad sport — one of the worst sports in the world, in fact — and I will attempt to prove that here.</p>
<a name="post-excerpt"></a><p>People often cite soccer’s popularity as a defense of the game and proof of its quality. This is an appeal to popularity, and it is a fallacy. Arguing that it is liked by a large number of people is not the same as arguing that it is good. A quick glance at the box office charts, or record sales, or television ratings will tell you all that you need to know about the validity of such an argument.</p>
<p>I want to begin with what I think is the strongest evidence against the sport of soccer. Let’s take a step back and say that we want to design the best game that we can given a couple simple criteria. The game must have two sides and must be symmetrical. That is to say that both sides start with exactly the same conditions. (In soccer this is true because both sides have the same number of players, the field is symmetrical, the win condition is symmetrical). Additionally, our game will have a point scoring mechanic which acts as the win condition, and we will also have a concept that only one side can score at a time. While one side is attempting to score, the second side is trying to prevent the first side from scoring. In essence, we have an offense and a defense. As you can see, these criteria apply to virtually every widely played team sport in the world.</p>
<p>One consideration that we have to make within our game is how difficult it will be for the offense to score. Obviously, the level of challenge for the defense is the inverse of this. The stronger you make the offense, the less interesting each individual offensive possession is. If the offense is very likely to score, then it is not very exciting when they do score, and instead a defensive hold impacts the game far more. And vice versa for a strong defensive game.</p>
<p>More importantly, the closer you come to an absolute offense (one in which the offense expects to score on every single possession), the less the difference in the ability of each team matters. If the offense scores 100% of the time no matter what, then a team of weaker players will still tie the stronger team every single time. As you approach that absolute, you are reducing the number of critical plays (in this case, defensive holds). The weaker team only needs to be successful a smaller number of times in order to tie or win the game, and you end up with a game that is poor at determining who is the better team. It becomes decided more by luck than skill. I think most people can agree that a great game is one in which the better team wins the majority of the time, and the larger the skill gap, the greater that majority becomes.</p>
<p>Thus, doesn’t it follow that in order to maximize a need for skill both on defense and offense, that we should weight these things exactly? That an offense matched up against an equally skilled defense should be successful half the time? Now, there is an argument to be made that offense is more exciting, so maybe it should be weighted slightly higher. Or that what makes offense exciting should come from its infrequency, so we should weight defense slightly higher. But we should not stray too far from that 50% mark.</p>
<p>In World Cup soccer, a team scores on average 1.25 goals per game. The most common score is 1-0. Clearly this game is heavily weighted for the defense. I could not find World Cup statistics, but in the English Premiere League, most teams average about 115 possessions per game. If the goal of an offense is to score, and the goal of a defense is to prevent a score, that means defenses are about 99% successful in soccer. Let’s compare that to the big four team sports in the United States:</p>
<p>In Major League Baseball’s 2013 season, teams averaged a score of 47.6% of their possessions. The National Football League had an offensive success rate of 33.6%. In the National Basketball Association, teams average about a point per possession. I could not find statistics on the average number of points gained on a possession when there’s a score, but I expect it to be about 2. Therefore, basketball comes very near that 50% weighted mark. In 2013-14, the National Hockey League saw about a 3.5% success rate. This sport clearly skews heavily defensive. Yet offenses are still successful 250% more often than in soccer.</p>
<p>Soccer is a poorly designed game. Defense is too strong, and the limited number of scoring possessions means a heavy reliance on luck and reduced opportunities to truly determine the better team. More subjectively, goals are exciting. By limiting them to such a degree, and by having such lengthy gaps in time between them, the sport itself becomes quite boring. Even a sport like basketball, with its 50% success rate, has exciting scoring. Watch any NBA game. The crowd will get just as amped after a crucial score as soccer fans after any goal. A sport doesn’t need such scarcity in scoring to remain exciting.</p>
<p>A spectator sport has to be judged by more than simply its rules, for they are not only meant to be played, but also to be viewed. A good spectator sport is fun to watch. Some can be an incredible experience to see live, but lose much of their appeal on a television. Others seem created for just such technology. Soccer, however, is bad in both environments.</p>
<p>The interesting thing about being at an arena or stadium for a game is that you and everyone else in attendance can actually impact the game. At a basketball or football game, the home team’s fans will make noise while their team is on defense, disrupting the communication that is crucial to running an offense in those sports. It is similar in baseball, though due to the slower nature of the game, fans usually wait until critical pitches or at bats. At a soccer game, on the other hand, fans make noise all the time. No matter what is happening on field. Their team could be on offense or defense. Play could be dead due to an out of bounds or a foul. The fans keep making the same noise. I went to a soccer game where a guy in the section next to mine played a drum the entire game, even during half time. The only impact it had on anything was the young girl (his daughter, presumably) sitting immediately next to him. She’s probably deaf now.</p>
<p>Soccer is also a bad television sport. It doesn’t have natural breaks in the action. Fouls are infrequent and out of bounds only delay the action for a couple seconds. This means there are not good times for advertisements. There are not good times for viewers to use the bathroom or refresh their snacks and beverages. Additionally, due to the length of the game and the lack of meaningful events (events that contribute to the win condition), there is not a lot of interesting commentary that can be made by the broadcasters. It is a sport from a bygone era, for a bygone era.</p>
<p>Speaking of age, soccer is very old. It was invented in the second century B.C. and is truly a product of its age. It requires minimal equipment, primitive groundskeeping, and has a simple ruleset. There were very few other sports that it had to succeed against or learn from. We have had over 2000 years of technological achievement, game theory, and trial and error since then. Better sports have been invented. Soccer is popular because it is old and humans love tradition. It is popular because it can be played in any corner of the civilized earth, no matter how poor or behind the times. If we have the resources, shouldn’t we play something better? We didn’t stop competitive video gaming at Pong or competitive board gaming at Checkers.</p>
<p>Not only was soccer invented before modern technology, the sport also refuses to embrace any advancements, even if they have an obvious benefit. The best example of this is the clock. For one thing, unlike any other timed sport I can think of, the clock ticks upward. Along with the score, this is the most critical piece of information about game state, and it requires unnecessary knowledge of the rules and a mental calculation of how much time is left. Further exasperating matters is stoppage time. Instead of pausing the clock, which absolutely every other timed sport in existence does and we’ve had the technology to do for centuries, soccer lets the time run even during stoppage. This is made up for with extra time at the end of the game. What is completely egregious is that quite often this information is kept hidden from the viewers and even the players. In essence, the referee is making an unchecked determination about when the game ends, and neither team can strategize around how much time is left, because it is unknown. Furthermore, it is anticlimactic to the fans. Last, it also creates opportunity for fraud. The fact that something so critical is not public information is the absolute worst aspect of modern soccer. It truly baffles me that people accept this as part of the game.</p>
<p>One notable aspect of any sport is how it handles tiebreakers. There are two groups. Either you continue playing the exact same game under a new ending limit, or you modify the sport and play something entirely different to satisfy the tie. The first method is the preferred method, because under the second you are no longer determining who is better at the sport itself, but rather the more skilled at a completely different game altogether. Soccer chooses this second method, changing the game completely and resorting to a penalty kick shootout. This removes the notion of defense, spacing, team play, and conditioning. Things that are critical pieces of the sport. Instead, you’re not determining who is the better soccer team, but rather which team has better penalty kickers. It’s a ridiculous way to select the winner of a soccer match, and it’s a result of the sport itself being so overwhelmingly defensive-oriented that a meaningful tiebreaker has been rejected as impractical. I’ve heard from fans that they love the tiebreaker because it’s “exciting”. This is an admittance that soccer itself is less exciting if not unexciting altogether. If that’s the case, it sounds like penalty kicks is the sport (some) people actually want.</p>
<p>My last point has to do with soccer in the United States, and specifically the World Cup. Professional level soccer continues to lag in popularity behind a number of other team sports in this country. However, during the World Cup, its popularity peaks and it becomes a topic of conversation amongst many who would never discuss it otherwise. News outlets cover the event even if they rarely cover any other soccer, including Major League Soccer, the United States’ largest professional league. The people in this country who have interest in the World Cup and only the World Cup when it comes to soccer invariably root for the United States’ team. Sure, that makes sense. But they aren’t rooting for players that they know or care about. They aren’t rooting for a style of play that they’re familiar with. They don’t know much of anything about soccer or the players or the coaches or any of it. All they know is the country which the team represents. So you have people blindly supporting a cause simply due to a common governing body and geolocation. This isn’t sports fandom. It’s nationalism. And I can not and will not support such an institution.</p>
<p>Soccer is a terrible game. It’s a terrible sport to watch live. It’s a terrible sport to watch on TV. It’s run by luddites. It encourages groupthink and unquestioned support. We have better sports to play and follow. There is no good reason for it to continue as anything more than a curiosity. It is the most popular sport in the world, and it sucks.</p>
]]></description><link>http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2014/06/15/soccer</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2014/06/15/soccer</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Steinberg]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lorde]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Lorde came out of nowhere last year, nowhere being a nickname for Middle Earth (more commonly known as New Zealand), with some nonsense song that is barely about a baseball team from Kansas City. What it’s mostly about isn’t baseball, but rather a hollow criticism of hip hop lyricism. Most specifically, the stunting and braggadocio that is ever-present across the genre.</p>
<a name="post-excerpt"></a><p>Many people with far more expertise on the subject have theorized on the different reasons why rap is so full of boasting, so I won’t embarrass myself by trying to offer my own ideas. Due to the pervasiveness of self-aggrandizing lyrics, rappers are having to get more creative. Their brags continue to grow both in outrageousness and sophistication. For most hip hop fans, this is a part of the fun.</p>
<p>Lorde apparently hates fun. Here are some lyrics from her song, “Royals.”</p>
<blockquote>
<p>But everybody’s like Cristal, Maybach, diamonds on your timepiece.<br>
Jet planes, islands, tigers on a gold leash.<br>
We don’t care, we aren’t caught up in your love affair.
<cite>Lorde - Royals</cite></p>
</blockquote>
<p>I don’t know who this “we” is that Lorde is referencing. Hip hop is increasing in popularity across the globe. Most of us are totally caught up in a love affair with a genre of music that rewards interesting lyrics. You know what’s not interesting? Her bitching about it. She doesn’t provide an explanation for why she’s unenthusiastic about the genre, nor does she offer an alternative. Unless her alternative is simply to complain. Maybe she should stop listening to songs she doesn’t like instead of spearheading an imaginary, directionless movement.</p>
<p>Lorde doesn’t stop there, however. A lot of the hip hop that gets played on national radio is party rap. The kind of thing you’d hear if you walked into a dance club. Oftentimes this music will present options to its listeners on what they can do to maximally enjoy the song with instructions like, “clap your hands” or “wave your arms.” Lorde calls out this second action explicitly in the song “Team”:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m kind of over getting told to throw my hands up in the air<br>
So there<br>
I’m kinda older than I was when I reveled without a care<br>
So there
<cite>Lorde - Team</cite></p>
</blockquote>
<p>She’s 17 now, by the way, and was even younger when she wrote those lyrics. It is unknown how young she must have been when she “reveled without a care”, but it must have been quite an early age. I’m twice as old as her, and I still enjoy throwing my hands in the air. To this day, if I hear ATLiens, my hands instinctively go up. So do everyone else’s born after the 1970s. Everyone else but Lorde, I guess.</p>
<p>So to recap, Lorde is tired bragging in hip hop, and she’s tired of being encouraged to have fun in hip hop. Maybe it’s time for Lorde face the fact that she is a sourpuss.</p>
<p>Part of her disaffiliation with hip hop lyrics is that she can’t relate to them because they speak of privilege, and she hails from more modest roots. Let’s examine that. Here are some lyrics from “Royals”:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>And I’m not proud of my address<br>
In the torn up town, no post code envy
<cite>Lorde - Royals</cite></p>
</blockquote>
<p>And from “Team”:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>We live in cities you’ll never see on screen<br>
Not very pretty, but we sure know how to run things
<cite>Lorde - Team</cite></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Lorde was raised in the city of Devonport, New Zealand, a suburb of Auckland. Here’s what Wikipedia has to say about Devonport:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>The suburb hosts the Devonport Naval Base of the Royal New Zealand Navy, the main facility for the country’s naval vessels, but is best known for its harbourside dining and drinking establishments and its heritage charm. In its scenery and setting, Devonport has been compared to Sausalito, California.
<cite><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Devonport,_New_Zealand">Wikipedia</a></cite></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Despite Lorde's claims, Devonport has been featured on screen. <a href="http://www.imdb.com/search/title?locations=Devonport,%20Auckland,%20New%20Zealand&amp;ref_=ttloc_loc_1">This</a> is IMDB's list of films and television shows that have been shot there.</p>
<p>And Sausalito? Here’s its description.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>…the city’s industrial character gave way in postwar years to a reputation as a wealthy and artistic enclave, a picturesque residential community (incorporating large numbers of houseboats), and a tourist destination.
<cite><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Devonport,_New_Zealand">Wikipedia</a></cite></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Sounds really torn up and ugly, Lorde. Now who is posturing? At least most of the rappers who talk about coming from the ghetto actually do come from the ghetto. What are you trying to accomplish here? Are you trying to relate to the lower class, the most traditional audience for hip hop? You’re walking into the belly of the beast in order to convince those who dwell there to rebel against the brand of music that most represents them? That’s ballsy, Lorde. Ballsy and stupid, because you have no argument and no basis for empathy.</p>
<p>More Royals lyrics:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>My friends and I we’ve cracked the code<br>
We count our dollars on the train to the party<br>
And everyone who knows us knows<br>
That we’re fine with this, we didn’t come from money
<cite>Lorde - Royals</cite></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Lorde attended a suburban school with a multimillion dollar endowment and a long list of famous alumni. I don’t know her family’s income, but I imagine it wasn’t terrible. And oh yeah, she signed a record deal when she was 13 years old. There’s no strict definition for coming from money, but I would bet most people in the world would say that Lorde came from enough means that these lyrics are false.</p>
<p>I dislike Lorde because she’s both inauthentic and a whiner. She hates on things that are dear to my heart with no argument for why. She lies about herself to garner support. I wish nothing but failure for her musical career, for people stop listening to her, and for the radio to go back to playing something that makes me feel an emotion besides anger.</p>
]]></description><link>http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2014/05/12/lorde</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2014/05/12/lorde</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Steinberg]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kevin Durant's 2014 MVP Speech]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Durant gave a speech upon winning the NBA MVP award this week. People are proclaiming his speech as “powerful”, “emotional”, and other words than indicate something far more impressive than what it was. They’re calling it the greatest MVP speech of all time. I think people wanted to be moved by it because everyone loves KD. He’s humble, he plays hard, he gives back to his community, he never speaks ill of his teammates, coaches, or really anyone. And oh yeah, he’s an incredibly good basketball player with an exciting game that results in a lot of points. He’s everything you want in a sports superstar.</p>
<a name="post-excerpt"></a><p>Somehow, despite all that, he was also the underdog. He broke LeBron James’ streak of MVPs. James is not as universally likeable as Durant. He betrayed his hometown team in a manner that seemed like he was intentionally inflicting as much pain as possible, as publicly as possible. He gave up on his small-market team of underdogs to stack the odds in his favor in Miami alongside other star players. He also is perhaps the most naturally athletic player in NBA history and hasn’t had to overcome anything. He’s an easy guy to root against. So not only does everyone love Durant, everyone wants to love Durant.</p>
<p>Everyone also wants to love Durant’s speech, and so they are unwilling to acknowledge one simple fact. Throughout his speech, in an effort to sound more dramatic, more humble, and more likeable somehow, KD lied out his ass.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>We moved so many different places growing up. It felt like a box. It felt like there was no getting out.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Ignoring the fact that moving a lot and feeling like you’re inside a box contradicts itself, you lived in Washington fucking DC. Not small town America. Not a third world country. In the capital of the world’s number one superpower. Shut the fuck up with you thought there was no getting out.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>My dream was to become a rec league coach.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Fuck you, Kevin, no it wasn’t. That isn’t anyone’s dream. Maybe that was your backup plan. Maybe if your playing career didn’t pan out, you wanted to coach kids. Sure, I can buy that. But it wasn’t your dream. If that was all you cared to be, you wouldn’t have been busting your ass since you were a pre-teen to be the best player that you could be.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I just never thought I could make it to college…</p>
</blockquote>
<p>You won a fucking AAU national championship when you were 11 years old. You were being recruited by colleges since before you went to high school. You were 6’9” in high school and First Team All American. You never thought? Ever?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>…NBA…</p>
</blockquote>
<p>You were the highest rated recruit in the country entering college. You won national player of the year in a landslide. Everyone knew you were a one and done. But you never thought you’d make it to the NBA? Ever?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I fell so many times, and got back up.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>When the fuck exactly did you fall? I mentioned your pre-high school, high school, and college success. You were also an instant star in the NBA. You’ve been considered the best scorer in the league for almost that entire time. You’ve never had a bad year. What, because you haven’t won the NBA Finals yet? That’s failing and getting back up? Forgive me for not shedding a fucking tear.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I went through the toughest times with my family.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Look, you come from a single parent family, I get it. Your mom worked hard. She sounds like a tremendous lady. But the toughest times? Toughest? Really? You had a roof. You had food. You received an education. You had after school programs. Your talent was recognized by the right people. You were able to pursue your dreams. I don’t know all of your family’s situation, but nothing that’s public seems to scream the “toughest times”.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>As a second grader, I had a Pistons Grant Hill jersey.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Fuck me, man. You had a Grant Hill jersey in second grade? I didn’t have a jersey in second grade. I wish I had it as tough as you.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Nick (Collison)…you believed in me from the beginning. You knew that I had potential.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>YOU WERE THE NATIONAL COLLEGIATE PLAYER OF THE YEAR AND THE SECOND PICK IN THE DRAFT. EVERYONE FUCKING KNEW YOU HAD POTENTIAL.</p>
<p>Kevin Durant is an amazing player and even better person. I get it. But don’t give me this bullshit about how great his speech was. It was manufactured horseshit.</p>
]]></description><link>http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2014/05/07/kevin-durant-s-2014-mvp-speech</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2014/05/07/kevin-durant-s-2014-mvp-speech</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Steinberg]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[JJ Abrams' Star Trek]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Before I begin my review, I need to make a confession. I didn't like this movie before it started. I have disliked it for months. Ever since the first preview that showed actual footage from the movie, I've thought it was going to be a disaster. I'll get into the why's as part of my review, but I just need to be clear that my expectations do not mean that I simply searched for justification as I viewed Star Trek, and that I ignored everything else that did not support my negative assumptions. In fact, there have been numerous cases where a movie far exceeded my initial thinking. In the interest of thoroughness, I'll even cite examples. My first impression of Gladiator was that it was going to be a lame Spartacus knockoff. It ended up being the best American action movie of this decade. I thought Rocky 6 was going to be as big a disgrace as Rocky 5. I ended up seeing it four times in the theaters. I thought Tropic Thunder would be just another lame Ben Stiller movie, and it's one of the funniest comedies I've seen in years. Yes, I make flash judgments. I believe that everyone does. The difference is that I'm not ashamed of it, and I'm as willing as anyone to change my thinking. All that being said, I was convinced that Star Trek would be utter crap, and I was right.</p>
<a name="post-excerpt"></a><p>I need to make another thing clear. I am not judging this in the context of other Star Trek movies. I don't care how bad those movies were. I don't care if you think this one is better. Just because you found the hooker with the mildest case of gonorrhea, it doesn't mean you found a good deal. I am judging this movie as a movie, and so should you. Either it's a good movie, or it's a bad movie, I don't care what it's called.</p>
<p>My first inkling that it would not be a good movie was based on the director, J.J. Abrams. You, the reader who thinks Star Trek belongs in the annals of the great Sci-Fi movies, need to first understand who directed it. This is the same man who wrote Armageddon, people. Armageddon! Do you remember Armageddon? Probably not. Your mind probably washed itself clean of all memories of this movie as a self-defense mechanism. That's ok, that's what I'm here for. Armageddon is factually one of the worst movies ever made. Everything about it is awful. And your sci-fi savior wrote it. But he didn't write Star Trek, he directed it. How does his early career as a writer qualify him as an action director? It doesn't. He's not a good director either. The only other movie he ever directed was Mission Impossible 3. I'd like to see you tell me you enjoyed that movie with a straight face. You didn't. I know you didn't. You know how I know you didn't? Because it fucking sucked, that's how. The only reason you watched it was because it had Philip Seymour Hoffman, and also you wanted to see if Michelle Monaghan got naked. I know this, because I'm just like you. He produced Cloverfield, a movie filmed so poorly that theaters had to put up signs warning you that the shitty cinematography (also known as Shaky Cam) could make you sick. You know what else J.J. Abrams is famous for? Lost. In some dialects, it is also known as The Most Overrated Show Ever Made. Yes, more overrated than ER. More overrated than Friends. More overrated than Family Guy. More overrated than American Idol. Well ok, not more than American Idol, but reality TV doesn't count. Lost started out interesting because it was big budget, an exotic location, lots of characters, and a sci-fi slant. It turns out that the characters all suck, the writers have no idea what the fuck they are doing, and the whole thing is a house of cards that was going to get knocked down eventually. J.J. Abrams' crown jewel is actually just a well-polished turd. This is the man who directed Star Trek. It's not really part of the review, but you all need to know this.</p>
<p>I'll get into the second reason why I thought it was going to be garbage in a bit, but the first thing I want to do is delve into the plot. A movie does not have to have a good plot in order to be enjoyable. Take Napoleon Dynamite for example. If you're going to sacrifice plot, you need to do something else extremely well. A comedy needs to be funny as hell. An action movie needs to have fantastically filmed action sequences and a swift pace. Dramas need to have infallible acting built upon solid character work. I think most people would define this Star Trek as an action movie, and I would say that is correct. We'll get to that. First, let's make sure the plot sucked.</p>
<p>Let's start with the crew of the Enterprise. An event happens which alters the history of Kirk-era Star Trek as we know it. OK. I understand why they did this. I don't agree with it, but I understand it. This way they can tell all new stories with the same characters without having to worry about contradictions, changes in character relationships, changes in personalities, changes in events, etc. In this reality, we're expected to believe that after only three years of school, Kirk gets promoted captain of what we're told is the brand new Flagship of the entire Federation fleet. He does this despite still being in school with at least another year to go under normal the normal Starfleet Academy courseload. He does this by somehow being appointed First Officer of the Enterprise only moments after making himself known to even be on board as, basically, a stowaway. He does this despite the fact that the fucking Flagship of the Federation ought to already have a god damn first officer. He does this despite the fact that even if it didn't, there were literally hundreds, if not thousands, of more qualified candidates on board. He does this because he makes one accurate assessment of one situation. So now he's the First Officer of the Flagship of the Federation fleet, and captain shortly thereafter.</p>
<p>We're expected to believe that despite the entire course of history changing, the exact same people end up as the highest ranking officers of the Enterprise. Sulu, who is young and with extremely limited real-world piloting experience, as evidenced by his rookie mistake in his very first act as pilot, is made the pilot of the Flagship of the Federation fleet. Bones, who has only been at Starfleet Academy as long as Kirk has, which is to say three years, is suddenly the chief medical officer of the Flagship of the Federation fleet. Checkov, who is 17 god damn years old, is suddenly the....well whatever the fuck his position is, working on the bridge of the Flagship of the Federation fleet. Scotty miraculously becomes the chief engineer of the Flagship of the Federation Fleet, despite the fact that he's nowhere even god damn close to working on the Enterprise when the movie begins. So we end up with the EXACT SAME crew as in the alternate reality. I understand why they did it, I just don't agree with it. It makes no god damned sense. At all.</p>
<p>So then, Captain Pike needs to send people trained in close range combat to fight the incredibly skilled at martial arts Romulan miners. He has an entire security staff whose sole purpose in life is to beat people's asses. Who does he send instead? His brand new First Officer and his god damned pilot! HIS PILOT!?!??! Are you fucking serious? These are the two people he sends? Not anyone from his fucking security staff???? And why is that? Oh, because we need to use the characters people care about. Fuck that. Who the fuck is writing this? Amateurs, that's who. This movie that you claim to love has a shitty fucking plot.</p>
<p>On the other side of the plot is the villain. The driving force behind the whole movie. The dude who sets everything into motion. Nero. A Romulan (and thus obviously evil). Is he a Romulan warrior? A military general? No. He's a fucking miner. Flying a mining ship. For some reason, the mining ship is about 100 times the size of the Enterprise. Whatever. That's not anywhere near the craziest part. This ship, for some reason, has incredible military capabilities. It has weapon systems that can, we are told, take down a fleet of Klingon warships. It handles Federation ships with ease. It can launch dozens of missiles simultaneously and disable many of the functions of enemy ships. Yes, I understand it's from a hundredish years in the future. Did you miss the part where it's A FUCKING MINING SHIP?</p>
<p>The story behind the ship is that they traveled back in time. To a specific point in time. Remember, they wanted to find Spock. They at least needed to travel backwards in time enough that their MINING SHIP could destroy the Federation's (and Klingon's, apparently) fleet of warships. Yet we also know that they could not control the destination point in time. This is evidenced by the fact that Spock doesn't return for another 25 years after them, going through the exact same black hole. So they just got really fucking lucky then? Ok, I guess so, everyone is getting really fucking lucky in this movie.</p>
<p>Why does Nero want to come back? At first, we think it's because Romulus was destroyed by the Federation. As it turns out, this is not true. It is destroyed by an inevitable supernova. The Federation wasn't even at fault. Nero didn't even blame the Federation. He blamed Spock. So does he come back to save Romulus? No, not exactly. Even though that would be quite easy. He actually seems most interested in coming back to get revenge on Spock by blowing up Vulcan. Ok. I guess that makes a little sense. Not a lot though, because he could fucking save Romulus, his wife, and his kids, and thus he wouldn't even have a grudge to really speak of anymore. But he's a stupid villain with no depth, so he wants revenge as stupid villains with no depth often do. But after he gets his revenge on Spock, now he wants to destroy the Federation? What? They never really explain this. They toss out something about how Romulus is tethered to the Federation and needs its help, and he wants to sever ties. They don't explain why that's true, or why that's bad in Nero's eyes. They just need something to continue the story now that Vulcan is blowed up. Of course his first target is Earth. I guess that's a coincidence, whatever. It still makes no fucking sense, and the writers don't even attempt to explain it. But that's what you get when you have a stupid villain with no depth who just walks around grumbling the whole time, and is well trained at fighting, along with his crew, because he's a miner. Or....what? I think the most amazing thing is they cast Eric Bana for this role and even he couldn't make it interesting. If Eric Bana cannot make your character interesting, then you suck as a writer, or as a director, or whatever else you do for the movie, because Eric Bana is a certified badass.</p>
<p>There's a lot of other stupid coincidence in this movie. Like Spock saving Kirk on the ice planet just in time. Or Nero attacking Kirk's father's ship right as his mother is giving birth in the most forced emotional scene in the movie. Or Scotty also being on this planet, and not too far from where Spock was marooned. Or Pike, the same predecessor of Kirk in the main timeline, being stationed for a short time in the same backwoods Iowa town where Kirk lives. Or Bones also being in that same town to start school at the exact same time as Kirk. Or Spock being the dude who wrote the Starfleet Bridge Officer test. Or Kirk banging (or attempting to) Uhura's roommate. Or Spock coming back in time at the same time as the Enterprise's maiden mission. Or Kirk listening to music that's over 100 years old so that the viewer can identify with it. Or Kirk jumping out of the car just in time and hanging on to the edge of the cliff. But I guess it's just a popcorn flick and we can ignore all that, right? I guess, if you're fucking braindead.</p>
<p>No but really, let's talk about that. It's a popcorn flick, but it's also an action movie. Now, if you're an action movie, it seems to me that one requirement should be that you have, you know, good action. If you are an action movie, and you have bad action, then you are a bad action movie. You may be a good comedy, because maybe it's funny, but it's a bad action movie. As an example of this, take Iron Man. Iron Man is funny as hell. If you ask yourself, is Iron Man a good comedy, you are inclined to say yes, because it's entertaining and funny. If you ask yourself if it's a good action movie, you would say no, because the action is not good (and in fact, there's only one real action scene to speak of). I've heard people use the following phrase in evaluating a movie: It's good for what it was. Usually I think they misuse the phrase, but I understand where they're coming from. If you're trying to be nothing but a popcorn flick, and you don't give a shit about plot or character or any other actual storytelling, then you can still be a good popcorn flick, and you can still be worth watching. You'll never be The Godfather, but that's ok. See Crank 2 as a recent example of this. So let's say Star Trek doesn't want to be a thinking man's space drama, as the older Star Treks attempted. Maybe it just wanted to be an effects-driven action movie. That's fine, for the most part. I don't know why it needs to be in the Star Trek universe. I understand why they want it to be, for the easier sell, but I don't agree with it.</p>
<p>Anyways, the question remains. How does Star Trek fare as an action movie? Fucking terrible, that's how. I'm something of an action movie snob. I love action movies. It may be my favorite genre. I surely watch more action movies than any other type of movie. And I can conclusively say that either I've seen a lot more action movies than J.J. Abrams has, or that he just doesn't pay any fucking attention while he watches them. Let me briefly describe to you, reader, how to film an action scene. The first step, and the most important step, is to choreograph. You choreograph the entire scene. You practice it over, and over, and over, and over, and over. You train the actors to do everything not requiring stunt-work. You plan out the camera cuts, the angles, everything. 90% of the work is in the preparation. Then, since your actors actually know what the fuck they're doing, and you know what the fuck you're doing, you film from a distance. You show everyone involved in the current fight, or the smaller skirmish if you're filming a large scale battle. You do long takes. A long take means that you let the actors perform multiple moves before editing in a new take. They have rehearsed it, they are actors, they can do this. If you want to add slow-motion, do so sparingly. Let the viewer see the impact. And most importantly, the viewer should always know exactly what is happening in a scene. They should know who the players are, they should know who is hitting who. They should know what's going on with the setting. This isn't a horror flick. They don't need an element of surprise. Let them watch the fucking scene. Here's what you don't do. You don't do close-ups during the action. In between, sure. Show the damage, show the fatigue, show the interspersed dialogue. But not during the fight. Never do close-ups during the fight. Also, never employ Shaky Cam. You know what Shaky Cam is. Shaky Cam was not invented by, but was popularized by the Bourne trilogy of movies. It's where the cameraman shakes the camera around for no reason in order to give you what a shitty fucking director thinks is a sense of realism, a sense of being part of the action. It also makes things easier on the director and actors. You see, when you do extreme close-ups with Shaky Cam and quick takes, you don't have to choreograph. Your actors don't have to train. They don't really have to do anything. It's lazy as shit, and anyone can do it. You can just film a lot of movement, because the consequence of these things is that you have no fucking idea what is going on, and you feel nauseous. Some people have even thrown up from Shaky Cam. As mentioned above, theaters have had to put warning signs at the box office about movies with Shaky Cam. Shaky Cam is a telltale sign that the director has no fucking idea how to film an action sequence.</p>
<p>Do you remember the action scenes in Star Trek? There were two chase scenes and the rest were close-up Shaky Cam. I felt sick. I had no idea what the fuck was going on at any time, and you didn't either. I know you didn't, because I'm better at watching action movies than you are. You didn't know what happened until it's all over. You still don't know what happened, you just know who won. If Star Trek is an action movie, which is how people want to label it, then it fucking fails. The action is horrid. Fucking Star Wars kid was filmed better than Star Trek, and that was a camcorder sitting on a tripod. And then you have the chase scenes. There was the stupid one on the ice planet that's not even worth talking about, and the car chase scene. The car chase scene ended with Kirk launching the car off of a cliff for no reason, jumping out at the last possible moment, barely hanging onto the edge, getting up, and giving a one-liner to the officer. You know what that was? I'll tell you what that was. That was a scene you'd expect to find in a Michael Bay movie. It was a, &quot;let's try to make this character look like an unbelievable badass, despite there not being any way that this person could possibly be this badass, and at no point in the future will this character ever be this badass again&quot; scene. You know who Michael Bay is. He's the man responsible for ruining more franchises than George Lucas. He's arguably the worst director in the world. You hate Michael Bay, and you hate his movies, because you do not have Down Syndrome. And if you do have Down Syndrome, there's still at least a 70% chance that you hate Michael Bay, because his movies are too retarded even for you. If you are a director, and any of the scenes in your movie feel like they were lifted out of a Michael Bay movie, then you suck balls. J.J. Abrams, you suck said balls.</p>
<p>People are wanting to say that this is the best Sci-Fi movie in years. You know what it takes to be truly good Sci-Fi? It's not just taking place in the future, or having lots of lasers, or space travel, or alien titties, or anything like that. Sci-Fi as a genre exists to challenge our established beliefs in the real world. Star Trek used to do that. The original series pushed more boundaries than almost any other television show ever made. It tackled all sorts of social issues that most other shows would never even dream of touching. That's what good Sci-Fi does. It makes us think. It makes us question. It makes us want to explore. Does the new Star Trek do any of that? No. Hell no. Because it does just want to be an action movie. Or a popcorn flick. Or a cash cow. Or whatever. Even if I can't convince you that it's not a good movie, which seriously, how the fuck is it not terrible, then at least you have to agree that it is not a pinnacle of Sci-Fi. It is simple. It doesn't challenge you as a viewer in any sense other than your ability to keep watching such a gigantic waste of money and talent.</p>
<p>I don't really want to talk about the acting for a few reasons. One is that I'm no judge of acting. Two is that there's even more subjectivity than in most of the other things I've talked about. And three is that I didn't really dislike any of the acting other than Zachary Quinto as Spock. Fortunately, Nimoy got to show him up throughout the movie as the way Spock should be played. Nimoy's Spock was logical, yes. Lacking in substantial emotion, sure. But there's that little bit of humanity in Spock that makes the character whole. Nimoy portrayed that humanity as a man eager for and appreciative of friendship. Supportive even when disagreed with. Trustworthy and perhaps even slightly optimistic. He was a character you liked and cared about, despite being robotic and plain-faced. Quinto's Spock, on the other hand, is a whiny bitch. He's just playing his role from Heroes. In Heroes, he is a villain. He's not a scary villain. He's not a deep villain. He's not a good villain. He's a whiny bitch villain. The only time you are ever scared of him is before you see his face and meet him as a person. He's just a name associated with a bunch of freaky murders. The name is scary. Then he comes on-screen and ruins it. Similarly, in Star Trek, the only time his Spock isn't a whiny bitch is before he gets any screen time. Once you meet him, from then on it's PMS city. On the other hand, the dude who played Bones was fucking great.</p>
<p>I like to summarize my reviews with metaphors, and I have two for you. The first one is from my Twitter review. Pretend you have an unassuming bare patch of dirt on the ground. A random person walks by the patch and takes a shit. As the day goes on, more and more people walk by this spot, see the shit, and decide that they will add to the pile by shitting on it themself. This happens again and again until the pile of shit has grown quite large. Somehow, maybe lightning strikes or the Hand of God comes into play, the pile of shit mutates into a movie. This is that movie. The second metaphor is as follows. The viewer is Scotty. J.J. Abrams is the fucked up midget alien that follows Scotty around and serves no real purpose except as a ridiculously lame attempt of humor, I guess. And the movie is the question you and Scotty are both asking of the midget alien/J.J. Abrams, which is, &quot;What the fuck are you doing here?&quot;</p>
]]></description><link>http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2009/05/10/jj-abrams-star-trek</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.epicaricacy.com/yfts/2009/05/10/jj-abrams-star-trek</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Steinberg]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2009 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>